We will move through Earth's horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
Let's fight for this blue sea and
let the wind take us far away.
Don't give up.
So I can come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this drop.
Sometimes we share.
Shut it up.
Do not be so afraid to podcast.
To have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times.
I'll try.
Look and breathe it out.
It's alright now.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to move them up.
We will move to our single horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We're a world from our heads.
We will win for sure.
Dreaming on.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the ones that
just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Become the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinite portions.
We will step up and we
will leave for sure.
So keep moving on.
He's wounded bad, but
he won't give up Shusui.
Will he making me work?
Lucky for me, he should be easy to track.
Give me back my damn sword!
I've had enough of this!
Is this place his house? What a dump.
I trust that your samurai associate
can deal with that monk fellow.
Though I wonder who he is,
other than a weapon thief.
I'm just so glad that you're alive.
All the rest can wait.
You've rendered me speechless.
I'm grateful that you care so much.
Step back, Lady Hiyori.
Curse it, Kaido.
It seems he wants every
last sword in the country.
Hey, see that over there?
They got racks!
Fill that green guy with lead!
Kappa style?
Yorikiri!
Kawamacho!
Are you all right?
My lady.
It happened so quickly.
I couldn't see.
No need to worry about me, Lady Hiyori.
Though I fear more
enemies may be on the way.
Let's get out of the open.
Yes, of course.
Hop on my back.
It's hard to walk in the snow.
Stop that.
Is this a joke, Kawamatsu?
I'm no child.
So you say.
But I've never seen an adult pout and
puff out their cheeks like a blowfish.
Oh, you're awful!
It brings back memories, doesn't it?
I never dared to dream that we'd
be walking side by side again.
There's so much I want
to talk to you about.
But first, why are you here?
It is a long and mundane tale.
But the first time I visited
was shortly after you left.
Since this was many years ago,
both Ringo and nearby Hakumai
were held by the Shimotsuki.
As you might recall, they were a
clan famed for their hardiness.
The daimyo's name was
Lord Shimotsuki Ushimaru.
He was well known as a master swordsman
and always shared his company with a fox.
A fox?
But in the end, like every other region,
Ringo was lost to Kaido and his forces.
My lady, have you heard of the eternal
graves erected here as a local tradition?
Yes.
Corpses are placed in caskets,
and they don't decompose for
centuries due to the cold.
That is correct.
And their locations are marked by
swords stabbed into the ground.
People in Ringo are given
a blade when they are born.
They will grow up with them and
keep them into old age as well.
When they die, the swords they
carried serve as their grave markers.
For all time, they're
inseparable from their swords.
So, of course, that is why
they're called Eternal Graves.
Unfortunately, since some of these
weapons here are famed blades,
grave robbing is quite often an issue.
This is simply a fact of life in Ringo.
Back to my story.
Allow me to tell you what
transpired here 13 years ago.
Having lost you, I prepared to
slice open my belly in shame.
Dammit, what the hell is that thing?
It must be a monster!
Forget about the swords! Run away!
This must be some samurai curse!
What a nuisance.
I've come a long way.
At least let me die in peace.
I know you. That's right.
If my memory serves me,
it was several years ago.
You must be Onimaru, correct?
Indeed,
the Komofox that stood before me was the
loyal companion of Lord
Shimotsuki Ushimaru,
the late daimyo of Ringo.
It can't be.
Oh, these graves.
Have you been protecting them on your own?
More than five years had passed
since the downfall of Ringo.
And all that time,
Onimaru alone had been
protecting the eternal
graves from thieves who
would take their swords.
Here.
No need to fear me.
I am your ally.
I see.
You are injured.
Onimaru!
Stay strong, my friend!
Oh-ho!
So you're finally awake.
Here, have some food.
I've been told that
fox is like fried tofu.
Oh?
Is something the matter?
You must eat, or your
wound will never heal.
Well, then how will you
protect your master's grave?
Don't be stubborn. Just take a bite.
I promise you'll like it.
You can trust me.
Ka-ba-ba!
Just a spot of indigestion, not to worry.
The food was so good I ate a bit too much.
Ka-ba-ba-ba!
Never mind my belly's rumbling.
Please, I do insist.
Oh, I knew it.
It is good.
I thought you might come.
We need not fight.
Forgive me.
I know how you feel.
Release me!
I don't expect you to
understand why I'm doing this.
Trust me when I tell you I do not
want to disturb the peace of the dead.
But right now, I must,
or this land will suffer.
Leave to the future.
Live on.
The fight for this country isn't over.
In 13 years, there will
be another great battle.
The day will come when the
samurai of this nation rise
again Standing proud in the
face of our adversaries But
their efforts will not bear
fruit without swords A great
many of them On the field of
battle When your comrade falls,
you take up their blade And carry
on The souls that reside in those
blades will empower the samurai
as they strike down their foes.
Until that day is won, this
land is still a battlefield!
Listen to me, Onimaru.
The battle between the
beast pirates and the
people of the land of
Wano is not over yet.
It is still too early to
lay these swords to rest.
In preparation for the
return of the samurai,
we must guard these swords and ensure that
the grave robbers don't take a single one?
all right?
Therefore, I'll collect every
blade myself, and hide them away!
I understand now, I've failed at my duty!
But I've been given a second chance!
This is the role I must fulfill!
Come back!
Lady Hiyori!
When I fail to protect Lady Hyori,
I plan to end my life in shame.
But I can't die yet, not
when there's work to be done,
not when I can be of use.
I have so much remorse;
if I don't keep busy,
it will consume me, if
you refuse to let go?
Bite off my damned arm!
Take it and eat it for all I care!
But I will not give up until I'm through!
Oh, my Mario.
What is this?
So you've had a change of heart already?
Could it be that you understood my words?
I won't complain.
Let's work together.
Thus,
Onimaru and I joined forces
to protect the graves
of the samurai and hide
their swords away for later.
All right, another day of robbing graves.
Rather frigid this morning, isn't it?
If it carries on like this, soon we
won't have any place left to sleep.
Perhaps we could dig a bit
of a cavern to hide them?
I'm famished.
If I sell a sword or two in
the capital, I could eat.
Imagine working on a full stomach and
not worrying about food every day.
Onimaru.
All in chest. Don't worry.
And yet, an army marches on its stomach.
This is for the greater good.
Forgive me.
I'm back, Onimaru.
I brought some food for
the two of us to share.
Look, your favorite.
Fried tofu.
Ooh!
I failed to see how we're
going to make money out here.
Bingo, are you sure this
plan's going to work?
Yes, I did my research on
these so-called eternal graves.
They're a treasure Traffy.
We can steal as many weapons as we like.
You see that?
Cross that bridge, and we'll
reach a massive grave site.
Ka-pa-pa!
Ka-pa-pa-pa!
Someone's there!
Begone, you robbers!
You shall not seize a single
blade from the soul of Ringo!
Not on my watch!
Bunch of nonsense! Bongo! Bongo! Attack!
Monimaru!
What is all this?
Who the hell are you?
You want to know my name?
Let me think.
You don't know?
Hmm...
Yes, perfect!
I am known as the Guardian
of Bandit's Bridge!
Oh!
You, dear, mad love!
Now, leave your weapons and go!
Or face my wrath!
Yuki Moria, that can't be a coincidence.
Same name, doing the same job?
To finish up the story,
I went to the capital a short time
later in order to acquire some food.
But after that, I was not able to return
to Ringo due to certain circumstances.
CITIZENS OF THE CAPITAL,
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST OF AN OPEN EDGE!
WE FINALLY CAUGHT YOU,
Belt FRIED Davy THIEVE!
NOW STOP RESISTING!
I'M A FULL, THIS IS THE
GRAVEST BLUNDER OF MY LIFE!
Forgive me, Onimaru.
And you were held captive for 13 years?
I let everyone down.
But wait, you're here because
you wanted to see that fox again?
Oh, no.
I'm sure if he's still alive that
Onimaru has given up on me by now.
It's been 13 years after all.
He must have felt betrayed.
What happened to that
monk you were fighting?
I wish I knew.
Last I saw, he went through this door.
But then he vanished into thin air.
Wait, through that door you said?
But this is...
What, you know something I don't know?
Where is he?
There's no doubt.
This house is where we lived back then.
The sword stash was here.
...Kalik. Huh?
Is that Kin'emon?
None other.
Greetings, my friend.
I am so pleased you're still alive.
I'm sure we both have
many stories to share.
But allow me to settle a
more pressing matter first.
You're aware that we've
conquered Udon, correct?
Yes, I am.
Raizo told me.
Although I do not know all the details,
I have heard that Sir Luffy's
extraordinary efforts.
won us a great many new recruits.
Now, you must be worried that
you don't have enough swords.
Yes, exactly so.
We are still plotting, but
there is no easy answer.
That wretched Orochi!
By robbing his country of its weapons,
he has stopped our plans
dead in their tracks.
Quite the predicament, yes.
But I have a solution.
You may gather thousands
of soldiers without fear.
I will provide as many
weapons as you need.
What? Truly?
I'll give you the location.
Send a team and see.
I'll make preparations to depart now.
How odd. What happened?
Onimaru couldn't have done this.
It would require a
human's hand, wouldn't it?
Sir Kawamatsu, I have fulfilled my duty.
The rest is up to you.
I wish you luck!
Only a week remains
before the day of the fire
festival when the samurai
will launch their raid.
On onigashima, fortunately,
Zoro and company have just acquired
a wealth of weapons for the.
impending battle.
Zoro Judo, that sword he took, if it
truly is Shusui, you should return it to
the land of Wano.
Not a chance!
I told you, it's my sword!
Then I'll give you a replacement.
Huh?
It is a sword that was handed down to me
from my late father, the famed blade Enma.
what was that it's a legendary sword
the only one that's ever injured kite
lady hyori no you cannot give
away a memento from lord oden
you may not know the tales but my father
was a skilled swordsman
in a two-sword style
wielding dual full-size blades when the
end was near the very
day before his execution
he entrusted his blades
to his children and
since he wielded dual swords in battle one
was given to momonosuke
and one was given to
me my brother's My
sword is Ame no Habekiri.
And my sword is Enma.
I promise you, they were both forged by
great swordsmiths who were once famous here.
You could not hope for a finer sword.
They are too fine! Can't you see?
This fellow may be strong, but
he's clearly quite dubious.
You can't entrust him
with Lord Odin's sword!
That's enough.
I know you feel strongly
about this matter.
But please do not disrespect
the man who saved my life.
Shusui belonged to Ryuma, who is
known as the God of the Blade.
I cannot fathom how it
fell into your hands.
Hmm.
Well, I guess Moria
did steal it after all.
Listen.
Juana wept when that sword was taken.
It's more than a blade to us.
It's a treasure.
Sacred.
Please allow Shusui to be
returned to its rightful place.
As long as you can give
me a replacement, fine.
But it is a shame.
You know, I shared a battle with Ryuma's
corpse, so I sort of feel a bond with him.
I'll give you Shusui back.
And I'll take Yenma.
But I also want to pay a
visit to Ryuma's gravesite?
You call this man trustworthy?
He seems rather delusional to me.
My lady.
The samurai arrested for rebelling against
the shogun orgy have yet to be released.
Yasui boldly sacrificed his
life in hopes of deceiving the
enemy and salvaging the samurai's
plan that orgy had uncovered.
I thought we settled this crap already.
We're not rebels.
Now let us out!
We had nothing to do with those flyers!
They were a prank by Lord Yasui!
The moon tattoo was just a popular design!
You think we're all rebels?
What is the Shogun so afraid of?
It's a disgrace to be put
on public display like
this as if we're some
sort of heinous criminals!
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves?
Just let us go!
What do you have to gain
from keeping us in here? Hey!
Damn it.
What else can we do?
I thought you were supposed to have
an alliance with Kate and Apoo.
Must not have worked out too well.
Since you were already licking
Kaido's boots by the time I got here.
The truth is, we were set up.
Scratchman Apu stabbed us in the back.
Or rather, he was working
for Kaido all along.
That monster Kaido stared
me in the eye and said.
If you want to become my
subordinate, I'll welcome you, boy.
He's always looking for strong warriors.
He wants to make the most
powerful army in the world after.
All my chances of victory in that
dire situation were zero percent.
My chances of successful
escape were zero percent.
My chances of survival
upon surrender were 40.
I didn't have much of a
choice.
Did I but kid and killer
lacked my judgment.
They challenged Kaido.
They fought and fought until they could
no longer so much as lift a finger.
Kaido won't kill men like
that because he desires
their strength rather
he'll attempt to crush
their spirits until they
become obedient but I
doubt that kid will ever
submit and so he'll die.
It's quite the pity
for his crew especially
orochi orders them to obey his whims vile
things I'm sure and if they don't oblige
they're told their captain will be killed.
The
four emperors truly are a
different breed than the rest of us.
They don't trifle with reason like we do.
Speaking of unreasonable, how
is your alliance with Straw Hat
staying by his side has brought
you all the way to wano?
Tell me, are you still
confident in that choice?
I'm asking the questions here!
Whatever your plot is, as long as it allows
me to escape, I'm not gonna complain.
Six days remain until
the raid on Onigashima.